Iryna Loushkina

Junior Fronted Developer

Profile

7+ years experience in many different projects, starting from sales/account management, implementation online booking tools to managing people.

Now, I am a self-taught junior frontend developer. I have been studying how to create responsive websites and environments connecting to that process.

My technology stack so far is HTML5, CSS3, SASS (SCSS syntax), basics of JavaScript (ES6), basics of PHP, mySQL, Git / GitHub, npm, Webpack, and the BEM methodology.

You are more than welcome to visit my portfolio https://iloush.github.io/irina_loushkina_cv/

Employment History

Junior Frontend Developer

February 2020 — Present

- Build websites for individuals and small business
- Create mobile-friendly layouts
- Create CSS animations and effects
- Add dynamic page functionality
- Build small clientside apps with JavaScript
- Use Browser Dev Tools (Chrome)
- Utilize Git / Github for version control
- Deploy and maintain small project

3D Modelling and Design, Ukraine

July 2018 — December 2019

Account Manager at Booking.com, Ukraine

July 2017 — June 2018

Senior Account Manager at American Express GBT, Ukraine

November 2015 — July 2017

Account Manager at American Express GBT, Ukraine

April 2014 — November 2015

Education

Bachelor degree of Economy, National Aviation Univesity, Ukraine

September 2007 — May 2011

Details

Amsterdam, +31 6 12 96 30 71 iloushkina@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin CV web page GitHub

Skills

HTML / CSS

SASS (SCSS syntax)

BEM methodology

JavaScript

PHP

mySQL

Git/GitHub

npm

Webpack

Adobe Photoshop

Languages

English

Ukrainian | Russian

Dutch

Hobbies

Biking, Running, Traveling, Cooking